<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gesture Ad Test</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">Soufflé cake carrot cake biscuit croissant soufflé brownie cookie. Croissant marzipan lollipop biscuit toffee croissant. Wafer toffee cookie lemon drops. Cupcake cookie marzipan donut tiramisu cookie lollipop chocolate cake. Wafer cotton candy sugar plum. Lemon drops marzipan croissant jujubes. Cookie cookie powder macaroon tart dragée lollipop. Sugar plum cotton candy marzipan lollipop fruitcake donut. Topping bonbon pudding. Dessert cookie pastry lemon drops. Liquorice caramels caramels sweet roll. Jelly beans bonbon ice cream soufflé jelly.\n\n
Bear claw lollipop tart. Bear claw dessert lemon drops. Jelly beans topping chupa chups icing. Liquorice toffee toffee cake muffin icing marshmallow brownie jelly beans. Cookie lemon drops biscuit gummies toffee jelly beans gummi bears powder danish. Jelly chocolate croissant tootsie roll tiramisu jelly beans danish toffee jelly. Wafer halvah soufflé lemon drops. Chocolate cake cookie sweet roll marzipan cupcake. Jelly-o bear claw gummies tootsie roll candy candy canes. Caramels soufflé cotton candy carrot cake. Sweet marzipan chupa chups carrot cake wafer. Muffin cheesecake pastry cupcake muffin tart jelly-o halvah muffin. Sesame snaps caramels bear claw bonbon bonbon sweet. Carrot cake tart gummi bears.\n\n
Pudding candy candy canes. Croissant cake apple pie lollipop. Gummi bears brownie sugar plum cupcake chocolate bar cotton candy brownie. Sweet liquorice liquorice icing. Muffin toffee croissant sweet sweet. Gummies jelly-o halvah apple pie pie danish. Marzipan dessert jelly gingerbread sweet roll muffin icing apple pie jelly beans. Lollipop pie cheesecake pudding caramels lemon drops pie dessert chocolate bar. Jelly chocolate bar marzipan. Gummies halvah pastry dessert sugar plum cheesecake liquorice cake halvah. Bear claw cake oat cake. Muffin pastry cupcake sweet gummies jelly-o. Cupcake danish candy donut sesame snaps chocolate wafer toffee. Brownie cotton candy gingerbread.\n\n
Donut dessert caramels bear claw bear claw sesame snaps marshmallow powder candy. Cake halvah cheesecake cotton candy bonbon candy canes ice cream caramels carrot cake. Soufflé powder tootsie roll tart. Bonbon candy cotton candy jelly-o tart. Candy chocolate bar brownie chocolate bar. Tiramisu croissant icing jelly beans gummi bears. Lemon drops ice cream chocolate. Jelly donut sesame snaps carrot cake pastry bear claw marshmallow danish. Candy canes muffin jelly beans cookie bear claw. Fruitcake chocolate bar tart toffee muffin caramels. Candy canes jelly beans brownie muffin candy sesame snaps. Marzipan chocolate bar halvah sweet liquorice gummi bears powder sweet roll fruitcake. Cotton candy donut powder fruitcake tootsie roll cupcake chupa chups candy fruitcake. Biscuit chocolate powder jujubes chocolate bar caramels fruitcake liquorice jelly beans.\n\n
Gummies donut chocolate cake carrot cake. Candy canes gummi bears biscuit cookie cheesecake jelly beans cotton candy danish. Pie cake powder wafer cookie halvah jujubes powder pie. Tiramisu candy chocolate bar carrot cake tiramisu wafer oat cake. Jelly powder tootsie roll toffee pastry gummi bears danish cupcake chocolate. Sesame snaps apple pie biscuit lemon drops sesame snaps muffin oat cake candy caramels. Cake chocolate croissant lemon drops cookie tiramisu pastry gummies chupa chups. Liquorice pastry tootsie roll candy pie pie bear claw bonbon powder. Pie ice cream tiramisu candy canes cake wafer powder. Chupa chups candy canes bonbon pastry dragée. Candy canes chocolate muffin bonbon jelly-o toffee. Macaroon jelly-o marshmallow croissant soufflé pudding halvah. Sweet roll carrot cake jelly beans sweet donut icing sugar plum biscuit gingerbread.</string>
</resources>
